# Kevin Lee

**Phone:** +1 (917) 765 0239 **Email:** Klee78736@gmail.com

## **Summary**

Senior Smart Contract Engineer and DeFi Specialist. Experienced with all stages of the Decentralized Finance App development, especially algorithmic stable coins, staking / yield farming and DAO. Wellversed in numerous programming languages including Solidity, JavaScript (TypeScript) and Python.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Solidity
- Hardhat
- Mocha
- Oracles (ChainLink)

- OpenZeppelin
- Tenderly
- JavaScript (TypeScript)
- Python

# **Experience**

## Smart Contract Developer - 7/2021 to 05/2022 Angle Money

- Worked on Stable Coin development using different tokens based on the oracles.
- Participated on Staking / Yield Farming products development.
- Built AMM for internal/external trades.
- Worked on Gauge Votes.

#### Smart Contract Developer - 10/2020 to 6/2021

Orca Avai

- Built DAO systems to make the DeFi app fully, community driven.
- Worked on Lending / Borrowing platforms using oracles.

## Smart Contract Developer - 01/2019 to 09/2020

#### **Loom Network**

- Worked successfully with diverse group of co-workers to accomplish goals and address issues related to their products and services (Smart Contracts for DAPP).
- Worked on smart contracts tutorial code snippet for content writers to complete Solidity Learning Tutorials.

### **Backend Developer** - 01/2016 to 12/2018

Alta Dynamics, Concord, MA

- Coded, tested and developed solutions in alignment with project requirements.
- Worked closely with business partners to create and deliver high-value solutions to meet their needs.

## **Education**

Bachelor of Computer Science: Nanyang Technological University

**Singapore (2011** – 2015)